Doug: “Alrighty. I already have a few people I can investigate…”
Doug: “Time to go find a murderer…”
Doug: I am SO cool!
Doug: “*woof* That buzzing again! Oh, it’s just Jade.” 
Doug: “Hey, Jade. What’s up?”
Jade: “I am sorry for not arriving yet. I’ll try to catch up with you soon.”
Jade: “I did manage to quickly gather some information on Norm and several people who were close to him.”
Jade: “I’ve sent all the info to your phone so you can check it whenever you need.”
Doug: “I’m still not used to all of this smartphone stuff, but I’ll definitely take a look at what you’ve sent me and jot down some notes on my trusty notepad.”
Jade: “*sigh* I’ll bring you over to the 21st century someday, Doug.”
Doug: “Who needs all of that technology? Like the great Holmes and Watson, I’m sure we can solve any case if we put our minds together.
Doug: “Bye Jade.”