Setting: The Scene of the Crime
Doug: Ah, the first murder scene I’ve actually been invited to investigate. It feels good to rise the ranks of the ace detective world.
Chief Punctum: “Look who finally made it. Good to have you here, Ace. As is plain to see, things… got pretty hairy.”
Doug: “Is now really the time for jokes, chief?”
Chief Punctum: “Aw, come now. Don’t be a grumpy greyhound. It’s always best to catch villains while in high spirits.”
Doug: She really is as far from being a noir detective as you can get. Sometimes I wish I had a more dramatic role model...
Doug: “Whatever you say, chief.”
Doug: “Anyway, thanks for letting me be a part of this investigation. Time to start investigating!”