Doug: “Um… Chief?”
Chief Punctum: “What? Is something the matter already, Ace?”
Doug: “So, I know I’m pretty new to the whole detective thing, but isn’t there normally… I don’t know… a dead body at the scene of a murder?”
Chief Punctum: “Good thing to notice there, Ace. There’s no body, but we’ve got a pool of blood big enough to swim in there. Nobody could lose that much blood and live, right?
Doug: “Yeah… but, how do we know it wasn’t somebody else who died? Or maybe his death was faked?”
Doug: “I don’t know; things seem like they’ll be so much more difficult without a dead body there to get evidence from.”
Chief Punctum: “Ah, it’s good to see you thinking like a detective. *sniff* You’re growing up so fast…”
Chief Punctum:  “Just rely on your detective’s instinct, and I’m sure you’ll be fine.” 
Doug: “Of course, chief. If there are any clues, I’ll sniff them out immediately.”