Doug: This will be a great chance to test my skills and find some juicy evidence.
Doug: Besides, there’s so much blood that the police will have more than enough to do all of their tests with.
*You touch the blood and rub it in between your fingers.*
Doug: “Hm…”
*You rub the blood between your fingers, faster now.*
Doug: “Hm……”
Doug: Isn’t blood supposed to be sticky? This feels pretty weird.
Doug: Anyway, that’s about all I’m getting from this. Wow, old school detectives must have been so good at all this blood-touching.
Doug: I should wipe it off of my fingers and find out what not-sticky blood may mean.
*You try to wipe the blood off of your fingers.*
Doug: Huh? It isn’t coming off…
*You try wiping it off harder and your hands are now completely covered in blood.*
Doug: Oh no! This was a bad idea! Bad idea!
Chief Punctum: “Looks like I’ve… caught you red-handed.”
Doug: “No! Chief, it’s not what it looks like! I’m so sor-- Wait a second, here…”
Chief Punctum: “You got an explanation for this, Ventose?”
Doug: This blood isn’t sticky, doesn’t wipe off, and is completely staining my fingers…
Doug: “Chief! I knew it!”
Chief Punctum: “This better be good…”
Doug: “I definitely thought that the blood looked a little weird, not to mention how much of it there was.”
Doug: “So… I was thinking that it wasn’t blood at all, so I touched it and my suspicions were confirmed!”
Chief Punctum: “Then what is it?”
Doug:  “It’s red ink, chief! It isn’t actually blood.”
Chief Punctum: “Wow, nice catch there, Ace. They say that us cats have good eyesight, but my old age might be getting to me. Great job figuring that out.”
Doug: “Of course! You can count on me!”
Doug:  Whew, she bought it…
Doug:  I really didn’t know what I was doing, but I accidentally discovered a major clue!
Doug:  Looks like my curiosity paid off today.