Jade: “Hm… I think we’ve analyzed the crime scene quite well for now.” 
Jade: “Since the police swept the place for evidence, then you did, and then we both did, it’s hard to imagine that any stone has been left unturned.”
Doug: “Good point. Now that we have so much evidence, we’ll have to piece together who the killer was.”
Jade: “We do, and yet I don’t believe we have an obvious culprit for the moment…”
Doug: “Yeah… Hm…”
Doug: “Hey, let’s go talk to the chief and see if she has anything else to tell us.”
Doug: “After that, we’ll have to start investigating suspects.”
Jade: “Sounds like a plan. Let’s head over to the police station.”
