Doug: “Ah, the classic murder scene. A room, a body, and wow that’s a LOT of blood.”
Chief Punctum: “Right on all counts there, Ace. You could practically swim in that pool of blood.”
Chief Punctum: “Don’t get squeamish on me now, though. You’ve got a lot of sleuthing to do today.”
Chief Punctum: “Plus, anything and everything in this room could be evidence, so don’t just focus on one thing.”
Doug: “Of course, chief. If there are any clues, I’ll sniff them out.”