Doug: Hm… it really is strange how much blood there is everywhere…
Doug: I know we’ve got a lot of the stuff flowing through our veins, but normally you don’t see this much of it at once; even at the scene of a murder.
Doug: This seems like a really important piece of evidence… so is there anything I can do to investigate further?
Doug: Oh! I know!
Doug: In some of those classic murder mysteries, the detective will take a little blood and rub it in between their fingers. 
Doug: Then, through sheer ingenuity, they will learn something about how the victim died.
Doug: Hm… I don’t know if I should do that, though.
Doug: The police have a bunch of new ways of analyzing blood these days, so the chief might get mad at me for ‘contaminating the evidence’ and whatnot.
Doug: It would be really cool if I could actually learn something from touching the blood like that, though…