Doug: I think that’s just about every piece of evidence there is to find here.
Doug: The chocolate and stuff I found make for good starting points of an investigation.
Doug: I should talk to the chief so I can start thinking about possible suspects.
Doug: “Hey chief, I think I’ve found almost everything that I need to start analyzing what happened here.”
Chief Punctum: “Yup, you sure left no bone unturned here, didn’t you?”
Doug: “So, the next thing I’d imagine I have to start handling are suspects and people who know what might have happened here.”
Chief Punctum: “You’re on the right track there, Ace. Is there anything I can do to help?”
Doug: “Well, since I found that chocolate, I was thinking that I should find the dealer who sold it to him. Only one person in this town comes to mind for that…”
Chief Punctum: “Tom ‘Sweet Tooth’ Confetto. That *meow* dog has eluded me for so many years.”
Chief Punctum: “Be very careful investigating him, Ace. He may seem like he’s a nice old dog at first, but he can turn on you at any moment.”
Chief Punctum: “And I don’t have to tell you the *meow* that drugs can do to your body, so our friend Norm might not have been quite himself when he died.”
Doug: “Don’t worry. If he was involved in any way with all this I’ll wring it out of him.” 
Chief Punctum: “Wow, just gonna waltz right up to the biggest chocolate dealer in town, huh? You got guts, Ace.”
Chief Punctum: “You can usually find him hanging out at his bar, The Sultry Saloon, relaxing with his confectionary confidantes.”
Doug: “Thanks for the info, chief. Got anything else I should know?”
Chief Punctum: “Norm worked for KT Corporation, those fat cats and dogs who own half of this city.”
Chief Punctum: “More specifically, he was hired by their law division, Weal Law Associates.”
Chief Punctum: “His coworkers and bosses there might know something about how he died, so you should sniff them out at some point.”