Jade: “Is this the room where poor Norm was murdered?”
Doug: “Well… about that…”
Doug: “There might very well have been a murder, but there doesn’t seem to be any body.”
Jade: “So you’re saying there’s a murder case and the body yet to be found? That sounds like exactly the sort of caper you’d love, Doug.”
Doug: “Normally it would be, but with no body, it doesn't quite feel like a murder, you know?”
Doug: “It makes me wonder if there even was one…”
Jade: “Well, that’s what we’re here to figure out.”