Doug: “Oh, and one more thing.”
Jade: “Yes?”
Doug: “I touched some of that blood on the floor earlier and--”
Jade: “What? You contaminated a crime scene?!”
Jade: “Doug, I know that some old detective somewhere probably did that, but you should know that we don't contaminate crime scenes these days. It can ruin the evidence!”
Doug: “Yeesh, calm down. You didn't even let me finish.”
Doug: “So I touched the ‘blood’ and it turned out to not be blood at all.”
Doug: “It’s actually red ink!”
Jade: “...”
Jade: “You just got lucky, didn't you?”
Doug: “That doesn't matter. All that matters is that I discovered an important piece of evidence.”
Jade: “True, but please be more careful in our current search of the place.”