Jade: “Wow, that’s a pool of blood big enough to swim in.”
Doug: “Ugh… First the chief, and now you?”
Jade: “She made the same joke, huh?”
Doug: “Yeah…”
Jade: “Ah, I should have known. She’s always one step ahead of my humor, that cat.”
Doug: “Yeah, she’s really... no joke.”
Jade: “You’re right. It’s no laughing matter.”
Doug: “We should probably just leave things to the pun-fessionals.”
Jade: “...”
Doug: “...”
Jade: “We should stop now, right?”
Doug: “Yeah, I think that’s a good idea.”
Jade: “Shall we continue the investigation?”
Doug: “Yeah. Hopefully we’re better with detective work than we are with puns.”
Jade: “That may be a problem for you, seeing as that pool isn’t what you think it is.”
Doug: “What do you mean?”
Jade: “Well, comparing that red pen you found to this “blood” on the floor makes one thing abundantly clear.”
Doug: “What do you mean?”
Jade: “The red liquid on the ground there looks to be the exact same substance that’s in this pen.”
Doug: “Norm wrote using his own blood?!”
Jade: “I really should be more direct with you, shouldn’t I?”
Jade: “What I meant was that the liquid on the floor is red ink, not blood.”
Doug: “Ohh, that explains a thing or two.”
Doug: “It was kinda weird that there was so much blood.”
Jade: “That’s certainly true, but we should remain cautious. That pool could be a mix of blood and ink meant to throw us off of the scent.”
Doug: “You’re right.”
Doug: “Let’s keep that in mind and continue the investigation.”