Jade: “Is this the room where poor Norm was murdered?”
Doug: “Well… about that…”
Doug: “Hey! What the…”
Jade: “What’s the matter? This seems like a perfectly normal scene of a murder.”
Jade: “There’s lots of blood and, of course, a body.”
Doug: “That’s the thing. Norm’s body wasn’t here before, but now it is.”
Doug: “How could a body disappear and reappear like that?”
Doug: “And the police have been around Norm’s place all day, so who could have gotten in and out of here to do it?”
Jade: “That’s a good question. Hopefully we can figure it all out.”
